

Mário Patrão

WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Hi, I'm Mário. A Portuguese web developer living in London for the past 5 years. As a .Net developer with +7 years of experience I'm now looking to embrace a new challenge that will allow me to grasp new technologies, augment my know-how and work with different "mind-sets".

SKILLS

JavaScript, C#, .NET

HTML 5

SQL Server, MySQL

Git, Team Foundation Server

Umbraco, Wordpress

Agile developement

Client liaison

Team management

CONTACT

mariopatrao@gmail.com +44 (0)7999 061551 Flat 5 Hexham Lodge 10-12 Mildmay Park N1 4PG, London

HOBBIES

Skate, gigs and pub quizzes

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER @ CTN COMMUNICATIONS

December 2014 -

At CTN I am integral to all aspects of the delivery of our client's digital projects. This includes:

- Back-end coding (mainly C#)
- Front-end coding of our client facing websites (Razor, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap)
- Implementation of webcasting platforms provisioned for the delivery of CTN's client's webcasting services
- Development of CTN's internal tools, from scoping through to delivery of the final product
- Maintain CTN digital infrastructure
- Working with brand consultants following a CTN rebrand to create a new vibrant website which can be viewed at https://embolden.agency/

I have worked with large blue-chip clients including M&S, Unilever, GlaxoSmithKline, RSA, GM&T among many others. On most occasions I am the direct contact for the client and work with them from conception to final delivery and execution.

WEB DEVELOPER @ ELEMENT 3 SOFTWARE

May 2012 - December 2013

At Element 3 I worked on different web solutions for housing developers to track end to end sales opportunities.

We also wrote a new web based document manager named FileHound. All this projects were written to be responsive and fast to convince large organizations to move their workflow into modern web based platforms.

WEB DEVELOPER @ PLANETA VIRTUAL

June 2009 - March 2012

Planeta Virtual is a software house specialized in web solutions. Its main product is a web solution that is responsible for the human resources, accounting and CRM implemented in several companies. I was responsible for multiple projects through the whole development cycle.

EDUCATION

INFORMATICS ENGINEERING @ FACULTY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY OF THE UNIVERSITY FERNANDO PESSOA OF PORTO

September 2002 - January 2009

COMPUTER SYSTEM ENGINEERING @ THE ACADEMY OF HUMANITIES AND ECONOMICS IN LODZ

September 2006 - July 2007